Edwin J. Feulner Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Organizations, 1957-2014 (Box 517-742)
  - National Commission on Economic Growth and Tax Reform
    - Public hearings, 1995, (3 folders) (Box 647)
    - Reports, 1996, (2 folders)
    - Research, 1995, (2 folders)
    - Schedules, 1995 (Box 648)
    - Solicited letters, 1995, (5 folders)
  - National Conservative Foundation, 1984-1986
  - National Forum Foundation, 1983-1990, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 649)
  - National Policy Forum, 1993-1994
  - Naval Postgraduate School, Monterey, Calif., 1984
  - Nockian Society, 1965-1971
  - Pacific Democratic Union, 1981-1986 See also Container 590, European Democratic Union; Containers 628-629, International Democratic Union, (1 folder) (Box 650)
  - Pepperdine University, Malibu, Calif.
    - Board of Visitors meetings
      - 2001-2005, (5 folders)
      - 2006-2014, (5 folders) (Box 651)
    - Conferences, 2005-2009, (2 folders)
    - General
      - 1995-2000
      - 2001-2014, (4 folders) (Box 652)
    - Miscellany, 1999-2012
  - Philadelphia Society
    - Administrative files
      - Bylaws, undated
      - Incorporation, 1965-1967
      - Membership
        - Lists, 1966-2002, (2 folders)
        - Nominations, 1979-1981 (Box 653)
      - Policy manual, 2014
    - Articles and mailings, 1965-1988
    - Financial records
      - 1964-1967, (6 folders)
      - 1968-1970, (9 folders) (Box 654)
      - 1971-1976, (2 folders) (Box 655)
    - General
      - 1964-1970, (8 folders)
      - 1971-1983, (11 folders) (Box 656)
      - 1984-1986, (6 folders) (Box 657)
      - 1987, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 658)
      - 1988-1992, (7 folders)
      - 1993-2011, (7 folders) (Box 659)
      - 2012, (1 folder) (Box 660)
      - 2013-2014, undated, (6 folders)
    - International Freedom Academy, 1965-1969, (2 folders) (Box 661)
  - President's Commission for the German-American Tricentennial, 1982-1983, (2 folders)
  - President's Commission on White House Fellows
    - Applications, 1981-1984
    - Commission members, 1981
    - General
      - 1981, (1 folder) (Box 662)
      - 1982-1987, (4 folders)
  - Public Diplomacy Collaborative at Harvard, Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass., 2009
  - Reagan Alumni Association, 1987-1989, 2007
  - Reform Club, London, England
    - American Circle, 2004-2007
    - Dinners
      - 1993-1994, (2 folders)
      - 1995-2002, (4 folders) (Box 663)
    - General
      - 1968-1981
      - 1993-2010, (2 folders) (Box 664)
    - Member lists, 2004-2012
    - Printed matter, 1974-2010, (2 folders)
  - Regis University, Denver, Colo.
    - Alumni Association
      - 1966-1969, (2 folders)
      - 1970-1973, (8 folders) (Box 665)
      - 1974-1978 (Box 666)
    - Board of Trustees
      - Manuals, 1992-1998, 2011, (5 folders)
      - Meetings (Box 667)
        - 1991-1994, (7 folders)
        - 1995-1997, (6 folders) (Box 668)
        - 1998-2000, (6 folders) (Box 669)
        - 2001-2005, (5 folders) (Box 670)
        - 2006, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 671)
        - 2007-2013, (7 folders)
    - Committees
      - Academic Affairs
        - 2005
        - 2006-2014, (3 folders) (Box 672)
      - Development and Public Affairs
        - 1991-1996, (4 folders)
        - 1997-1998, (2 folders) (Box 673)
      - Financial and Business Affairs, 1997-2001, (4 folders)
      - Inaugural, 1993, (1 folder) (Box 674)
      - New Ventures, 1993-2000, (4 folders)
    - Executive summaries
      - 1991-2006, (3 folders)
      - 2007-2013, (2 folders) (Box 675)
    - Financial records
      - 1989-1997, (6 folders)
      - 1997-2008, (5 folders) (Box 676)
    - Forum on the Future, 1999-2000, (1 folder) (Box 677)
    - General
      - 1989-1993, (7 folders)
      - 1994-1995, (7 folders) (Box 678)
      - 1996-2000, (8 folders) (Box 679)
      - 2001-2013, (6 folders) (Box 680)
    - National Commission on the Future of Regis College, 1981-1983, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 681)
    - President's report to the board, 1991-1992, (2 folders)
    - Printed matter, 1981-1998, (3 folders) (Box 682)
    - Reports, 1991-2008, (3 folders) (Box 683)
  - Rockford Institute, circa 1981-1990
  - Roe Foundation
    - 1982-1983, (2 folders)
    - 1984-1989, 1995, (10 folders)
    - 2002-2009, (8 folders) (Box 684)
    - 2010-2013, (4 folders) (Box 685)
  - St. James School, St. James, Md. (Box 686)
    - General
      - 1989-1992, (4 folders)
      - 1993-1997, undated, (3 folders) (Box 687)
    - Financial records, 1990-1996
    - Planning binder, 1994, (2 folders)
  - Sarah Scaife Foundation (Box 688)
    - Board of Trustees meetings
      - 1991-1992, (6 folders)
      - 1993-1994, (6 folders) (Box 689)
      - 1995, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 690)
      - 1996, (2 folders)
      - 1997, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 691)
      - 1998, (3 folders)
      - 1999, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 692)
      - 2000-2001, (6 folders)
      - 2003-2005, (6 folders) (Box 693)
      - 2006-2007, (4 folders) (Box 694)
      - 2008, (1 folder) (Box 695)
      - 2009-2010, (4 folders)
      - 2011-2012, (4 folders) (Box 696)
      - 2013, (1 folder) (Box 697)
      - 2014
    - Financial records
      - 1987-1999, (4 folders)
      - 2000-2009, (5 folders) (Box 698)
      - 2011-2012, (2 folders) (Box 699)
    - Miscellany, 2004-2008
    - Proposals, 1991-2007
  - Sequoia National Bank See also Containers 580-589, Credit International Bank
    - Board of Directors meetings
      - 1994
        - Feb., (3 folders)
        - Mar.-June, (5 folders) (Box 700)
      - 1995, Jan.
      - 1996
        - May, (2 folders)
        - Nov. (Box 701)
      - 1997, Apr.-Aug., (4 folders)
    - Compliance Committee
      - 1995, (5 folders)
      - 1996, (2 folders) (Box 702)
    - Financial records, 1993-2000, (5 folders)
    - General
      - 1994
      - 1995-2000, (4 folders) (Box 703)
    - Loans, 1994-1997, (3 folders)
    - Miscellany, undated (Box 704)
    - Reports
      - Branch sale memorandum, 1995
      - Building for the Future, 1994
      - Classified asset variance, 1992-1994
      - Contingency capital plan, 1995
      - General asset/liability management policy, 1994, (2 folders)
      - Lending function evaluation, 1996
      - Loan portfolio review report by Risk Management Group, 1995
      - Looking to the Future, 1998
      - Management study, 1995
      - Report of examination, 1994-1998, (2 folders) (Box 705)
      - Revised investment policy and loan policy manual, 1994, (2 folders)
      - Stock option plan, 1995
      - Stock valuation, 1997
      - Strategic plans, 1994-1996, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 706)
  - Southern Economic Association, 1966-1967
  - Sovereign Military Order of Malta, 1985-2003, (2 folders)
  - Stephen Decatur Society, 1965-1969
  - Union League Club, New York, N.Y., 1979-2008, (2 folders)
  - United Nations Second Special Session on Disarmament, 1982 (Box 707)
    - Briefing
    - Committee report
    - Miscellany
    - Newspaper clippings
    - Statements
  - United States Advisory Commission on Public Diplomacy
    - Memoranda and meetings
      - 1982
        - Jan.-Oct., (4 folders)
        - Nov.-Dec., (4 folders) (Box 708)
      - 1983
        - Jan.-July, (6 folders)
        - Aug-Dec., (6 folders) (Box 709)
      - 1984
        - Jan., (2 folders)
        - Feb.-May, (8 folders) (Box 710)
        - June-Dec., (6 folders) (Box 711)
      - 1985
        - Jan.-Apr., (3 folders)
        - May-Dec., (8 folders) (Box 712)
      - 1986 (Box 713)
        - Jan.-May, (6 folders)
        - June-Dec., (9 folders) (Box 714)
      - 1987 (Box 715)
        - Jan.-May, (7 folders)
        - June-Dec., (8 folders) (Box 716)
      - 1988
        - Jan.-Feb., (2 folders)
        - Mar.-Dec., (9 folders) (Box 717)
      - 1989
        - Jan.
        - Feb.-Sept., (7 folders) (Box 718)
        - Oct.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box 719)
      - 1990
        - Jan.-July, (7 folders)
        - Aug.-Dec. (4 folders (Box 720)
      - 1991
        - Jan.-July, (5 folders)
        - Sept.-Dec., (3 folders) (Box 721)
      - 1992
        - Jan.-June, (7 folders)
        - July-Dec., (5 folders) (Box 722)
      - 1993
        - Jan.-Oct., (5 folders)
        - Nov.-Dec. (Box 723)
      - 1994-1998, (2 folders)
    - Miscellany
      - Agency updates, 1996-1997
      - Bylaws, undated
      - Congressional hearings, 1984-1991, (3 folders)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1982-1990, (1 folder); (4 folders) (Box 724)
      - Speeches and writings by Feulner, 1984-1985
    - Reports
      - 1980-1982, (3 folders)
      - 1983-1986, (6 folders) (Box 725)
      - 1987-1991, (6 folders) (Box 726)
      - 1992-1995, undated, (3 folders) (Box 727)
    - Subject file
      - Conference on Public Diplomacy in the Information Age, Washington, D.C., 1987, (4 folders)
      - East-West Center, 1981-1984, (3 folders) (Box 728)
      - International Communication Agency, 1981-1982, (2 folders)
      - National Endowment for Democracy, 1983-1985, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 729)
      - New Directions Advisory Committee, 1981-1982, (2 folders)
      - Radio Free Asia, 1991-1992
      - Radio Free Europe, 1988-1990 (Box 730)
      - Radio Marti, 1983-1985
      - United States Information Agency, 1983-1986, (3 folders)
      - Voice of America, 1982-1993, (2 folders); (6 folders) (Box 731)
      - Wick, Charles, 1983-1984, (3 folders) (Box 732)
      - Worldnet, 1983-1986, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 733)
    - Travel file
      - 1980-1984, (5 folders)
      - 1985, (1 folder) (Box 734)
      - 1986-1993, (3 folders)
  - United States Commission on Improving the Effectiveness of the United Nations
    - General, 1992-1993, (2 folders)
    - Meetings, 1992-1993
    - Miscellany, 1990-1992
    - Report and drafts, 1993, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 735)
    - Research, 1989-1993, (2 folders)
  - United States Information Agency See Containers 707-734, United States Advisory Commission on Public Diplomacy
  - United States Reform Observation Panel for UNESCO, 1985-1990, (2 folders)
  - University Club, Washington, D.C., 1968-1976 (Box 736)
  - University of Edinburgh, Edinburgh, Scotland
    - American Friends of the University of Edinburgh, 1982-1999, (3 folders)
    - University of Edinburgh USA Development Trust
      - 1992-1994, (4 folders)
      - 1995-2006, (10 folders) (Box 737)
      - 2007-2013, (7 folders) (Box 738)
  - Victims of Communism Memorial Foundation, 1995-2011 (Box 739)
  - Vietnam Council on Foreign Relations, 1973-1975, (4 folders)
  - Wharton Graduate School Club of Washington, Washington, D.C., 1966-1971, 1981, 1993-2000, (3 folders) (Box 740)
  - William E. Simon Foundation Prize, 2000-2008, (2 folders)
  - Windsor Foundation (Box 741)
    - 1993-1994, (3 folders)
    - 1995, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 742)
    - 1996-1997
  - World Economic Forum, 1988-2012, (3 folders)
- Other Professional Files, 1947-2003 (Box 743-800)
  Correspondence, memoranda, reports, briefing books, subject files, and other papers pertaining to Feulner's professional employment in the years prior to 1977 and assignments in later years outside of the Heritage Foundation. Focusing primarily on conservative public policy, a major portion of the files relate to his work in the United States House of Representatives, with largest portion focusing on Feulner's years as executive director of the Republican Study Committee.
  Arranged alphabetically by place of employment and therein by topic or type of material, except for a subject file that is arranged alphabetically by topic.
  - Center for Strategic Studies, Georgetown University, Washington, D.C. (Box 743)
    - Africa, 1965-1966
    - Balance of payments, 1965-1966
    - Congressional briefings, 1966
    - Correspondence, 1965-1966
    - Expenses, 1965-1967
    - Job possibilities, 1966
    - Memoranda, 1965-1967
    - Miscellany, 1965-1968
    - Staff meetings, 1965-1966
    - Transport, 1963-1966
    - Transportation Department, 1966
  - Crane, Philip M., congressional staff
    - American Medical Association, 1974
    - Brezhnev Doctrine symposium, Warrenton, Va., 1970
    - Charles Edison Memorial Youth Fund, Chinese refugees, 1971-1972
    - Committee on Committees, 1971 (Box 744)
    - Committee on House Administration, 1973
    - Correspondence, 1970-1973
      - Crane
      - Feulner
    - Crane for Congress campaign, 1971-1972, (2 folders)
    - Derwinski, Edward J., whip calls, 1971
    - Diebold Institute for Public Policy Studies, 1971-1974
    - Economic issues, 1969-1971, (2 folders)
    - Gold, 1971
    - Hiring of Feulner, 1969-1971 (Box 745)
    - Housing and Urban Development Department, 1968-1972
    - "Kids and other assorted social problems," 1968-1971
    - Labor, 1969-1971
    - Middle East, 1970-1971
    - Miscellany, 1968-1974, (4 folders)
    - Office procedures, 1971-1972 (Box 746)
    - Panama Canal, 1963-1973, (2 folders)
    - Pending, 1972-1974
    - Postal patron questionnaire, 1969-1970
    - Radio and television, 1971
    - Research material, 1957, 1970
    - "Sounding Board" column, 1971
    - Speeches, 1968-circa 1970
    - Supersonic transport, 1971
    - Talent bank, 1974
    - Tax reform, 1971-1972
    - Trade, 1970-1973, (4 folders) (Box 747)
    - Twenty-second Congressional district, Illinois, 1971
    - Vietnam
      - Con Son prison, 1968-1970, (4 folders)
      - General, 1965-1972, (2 folders) (Box 748)
      - Trip, 1970
  - Defense Department staff
    - Anti-ballistic missile, 1969
    - Miscellany, 1969-1970
  - House Republican Conference
    - Correspondence, 1967-1969
    - East-West relations, 1967-1968, (2 folders)
    - Economic advisories, 1968
    - Federal aid to state and local governments, 1967
    - Garbuny, Siegfried, 1967-1968
    - Independent action, 1967-1968 (Box 749)
    - Nixon, Richard M., 1962-1968
    - Republican Task Force on East-West Trade
      - Congressional statements, 1966-1967
      - Correspondence, 1967-1968
      - Export-Import Bank, 1967-1968
      - For distribution to members, 1967
      - Gravity meter, 1967
      - Improdmash-67 trade fair, Moscow, USSR, 1967
      - Kelly, Edna F., hearings, 1967-1968
      - Latta, Delbert L., 1967-1968
      - Legislation, 1966-1969
      - Meetings, 1967-1968
      - Memoranda, 1967-1969 (Box 750)
      - Press releases, 1967-1968
      - Select Committee resolution, 1967
  - Kemp, Jack, vice presidential campaign, 1996
    - Bennett, William J., project
    - Capital gains indexing
    - Catholics for Dole/Kemp
    - Conservative groups meeting
    - Correspondence, (2 folders)
    - Debate
      - Briefing book, (2 folders)
      - Issues, (2 folders) (Box 751)
      - Miscellany
      - Preparation, (3 folders)
    - Economic plan, (2 folders)
    - Fact sheets and press releases
    - Irish-American presidential forum (Box 752)
    - Memoranda, (2 folders)
    - Miscellany, (3 folders)
    - Notes
    - Partial birth abortion
    - Personal
    - Schedules (Box 753)
      - Aug.-Oct., (8 folders)
      - Nov. (Box 754)
    - Speeches
  - Laird, Melvin R., public affairs fellowship
    - Feulner projects as seen in Congressional Record, 1967-1968
    - Hoover Institution on War, Revolution and Peace, 1967-1968
    - House Concurrent Resolution 210, Ninetieth Congress, first session, 1966-1968, (2 folders)
    - Inflation memoranda, 1967
    - Miscellany, 1965-1968
    - Revenue sharing, 1967-1968
    - Speeches, 1966-1967
    - Wood County project, Wisconsin, 1965-1970, (1 folder); (5 folders) (Box 755)
  - Reagan, Ronald, administration
    - Consultancies
      - 1982
        - Management meetings
        - Memoranda
          - Feulner to Edwin Meese, (1 folder) (Box 756)
          - Miscellaneous, (2 folders)
        - Miscellany, (3 folders)
        - Notebooks
          - Office of Policy Development orientation material
          - Presidential statements, (2 folders) (Box 757)
          - Social issues
      - 1987, (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box 758)
    - Transition team
      - Correspondence and memoranda
        - 1980, (5 folders)
        - 1981, undated, (2 folders) (Box 759)
      - International financial institutions report, 1980
      - Miscellany, 1978-1980, (2 folders)
      - Press clippings, 1980-1981, (5 folders)
      - Resource material, 1977-1980, (4 folders) (Box 760)
  - Republican Study Committee
    - Alphabetical file, 1974-1977
      - A-B, (4 folders)
      - C-G, (10 folders) (Box 761)
      - H-S, (11 folders) (Box 762)
      - T-Z, (2 folders) (Box 763)
    - American Conservative Union, 1975
    - Annual reports, 1974-1985, (2 folders)
    - Bicentennial conference series on America's economic heritage, proposed, 1975
    - Blackburn, Benjamin B., nomination as chairman of Federal Home Loan Bank Board, 1975
    - Briefing books
      - 1975, (3 folders)
      - 1976, (2 folders) (Box 764)
      - 1977
        - Jan.-Aug., (4 folders)
        - Sept.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box 765)
      - 1978-1979, (6 folders)
    - Business cards, circa 1974-1976 (Box 766)
    - Campaign Fund
      - Campaign packets, 1976, (3 folders)
      - Candidates, Republican, 1976, (2 folders)
      - Candidates' campaign material, 1976
      - The Case Against the Reckless Congress, 1974-1977, (1 folder); (5 folders) (Box 767)
      - Miscellany, 1976-1978, (4 folders)
      - Opposition research, 1976, (3 folders) (Box 768)
    - Cantrell, Tom, 1974-1975
    - Captive Nations Week, 1975
    - Center for Advanced International Studies, University of Miami, Coral Gables, Fla., 1975
    - Chamber of Congress of the United States, 1973-1976
    - China
      - 1971-1975, (2 folders)
      - 1976, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 769)
    - China and South Africa seminars, 1976, (2 folders)
    - Committee for the Survival of a Free Congress, 1975-1977, (3 folders)
    - Committee of Nine, 1974-1976
    - Common Cause, 1975-1976, (2 folders)
    - Confidential memoranda, 1974-1976 (Box 770)
    - Council on American Affairs, 1975-1976
    - Crane, Philip M., 1974-1976
    - Daily activities reports
      - 1975, Oct.-Dec., (2 folders)
      - 1976
        - Jan.-May, (6 folders)
        - June-Dec., (7 folders) (Box 771)
      - 1977, Jan.-Mar., (3 folders)
    - Democratic Study Group, 1975 (Box 772)
    - Downtown intelligence reports, 1974
    - Elections, 1974-1976, (6 folders)
    - "Figuring Out America: Useful Facts and Figures"
      - 1978-1980
      - 1982 (Box 773)
    - Future projects, 1975
    - Gold, 1972-1975, (7 folders)
    - History project, 1977 (Box 774)
    - House bills and votes, 1976, (2 folders)
    - Intelligence Digest, 1975
    - International Institute for Strategic Studies, 1975-1976
    - International Monetary Fund, 1976
    - Jaycees, 1975
    - Job descriptions, 1975-1976
    - Junkets, 1972-1977, (5 folders)
    - Key issues, 1976-1977, 1982, (2 folders) (Box 775)
    - Kissinger, Henry, meeting, 1976, (2 folders)
    - Korea
      - 1973-1974
      - 1975, (4 folders); (1 folder) (Box 776)
      - 1976-1978, (3 folders)
    - Lists, 1976-1977
    - Major bill tracking summary, 1975-1976
    - Manuals and handbooks
      - 1974, (2 folders)
      - 1976-1978, (3 folders) (Box 777)
    - Measures of economic freedom research project, 1976
    - Memoranda, notes, and reminders, 1973-1975
    - Meetings, annual, Executive Committee, and members, 1974-1977, 1985, (6 folders)
    - Members' special requests, 1974
    - Miller, Daphne, 1974-1978, (6 folders) (Box 778)
    - National Association of Manufacturers, 1972-1976
    - New International Economic Order, 1976, (2 folders); (4 folders) (Box 779)
    - Nixon, Richard M., meeting, 1973
    - Panama, 1959-1966, 1974-1976, (5 folders); (2 folders) (Box 780)
    - Payroll and salary reports, 1973-1976, (3 folders)
    - Placement and referral reports, 1974
    - Political reports, 1974-1976
    - Portugal, 1975
    - Press clippings, 1973-1977
    - Printed matter, 1974-1976, (2 folders)
    - Republican Platform Committee, 1976 (Box 781)
      - Administration
      - Committee appointments and delegates lists, (2 folders)
      - Democratic platform
      - Full committee material
      - Miscellany, (3 folders)
      - Subcommittee drafts, (3 folders) (Box 782)
      - Subcommittee research
    - Research guides and directories, 1975-1977, (2 folders)
    - Résumés, 1974-1976
    - Rhodesia, 1975-1976
    - Routine votes, 1974
    - "Sales pitches," 1973
    - Select Committee on Committees, 1974
    - South Africa
      - 1966, 1972-1973
      - 1974-1975, (4 folders) (Box 783)
      - 1976, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 784)
      - 1977
    - Staff biographies, undated
    - Statement of purpose and general information, circa 1974-1975
    - Stockman, David Alan, 1975-1976
    - Third party, 1974-1976
    - Trade, 1974
    - Trial basis members, 1974
    - United Nations
      - General, 1947-1948, 1971-1976, (4 folders); (3 folders) (Box 785)
      - Korea, 1973-1975, (2 folders)
      - South Africa, 1969-1976, (2 folders)
    - Vietnam, 1974-1975, (2 folders) (Box 786)
    - Vote justifications, 1974-1976, (2 folders)
    - Work papers
      - 1973, (3 folders)
      - 1974
        - Jan.-Mar., (2 folders)
        - Apr.-Dec., (8 folders) (Box 787)
        - No month (Box 788)
      - 1975
        - Jan.-Aug., (8 folders)
        - Sept.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box 789)
        - No month
      - 1976
        - Jan.-May, (5 folders)
        - June-Dec., (9 folders) (Box 790)
      - 1977-1978, 1985, undated, (5 folders) (Box 791)
  - Schuchman Foundation Center for the Public Interest
    - Board meetings, 1972-1974
    - Budget, 1973
    - "Dog and pony" shows, 1973-1974
    - Fund-raising, 1973-1974, (4 folders)
    - General
      - 1972
      - 1973-1974, (6 folders) (Box 792)
    - Grassroots operation, 1973
    - Heritage Foundation, 1973
    - Internal memoranda, 1973-1974, (2 folders)
    - Memoranda for the file, 1973-1974, (2 folders)
    - Onstott, Howard R., 1973 (Box 793)
    - Personal messages, 1973
    - Prospects, 1973
    - Prospectus, 1972
    - Public Policy Issues, monographs, 1973, (2 folders)
    - Robert M. Schuchman Memorial Foundation, 1967-1973, (3 folders)
    - Scaife Family Charitable Trusts, 1973-1974
  - Subject file
    - Allen, Richard V., 1967-1969
    - American Association for the Advancement of Slavic Studies, Washington, D.C., chapter, 1966-1967
    - American Economic Association, 1965-1966
    - Broadcasting Board of Governors, 1998
    - Bull Elephants, 1974-1976
    - Chicago and North Western Railway Company, 1971
    - China, 1966-1973, (3 folders) (Box 794)
    - Civil Aeronautics Board, 1964-1970, (2 folders)
    - Communist economics, 1969
    - Congressional Secretaries Club, Washington, D.C., 1968
    - Cuba, 1967-1968
    - Czechoslovakia, 1968
    - Defense, 1965-1969, (2 folders)
    - East-West trade
      - Administration position, 1966-1970
      - Congressional opinions
        - 1965-1966
        - 1967-1971, (2 folders) (Box 795)
      - Export controls, 1966-1969, (2 folders)
      - General, 1964-1971, 1977, (4 folders)
      - Legislative activities, Ninety-first Congress, 1969 (Box 796)
      - Sanctions, 1967-1968
      - Trade with China, 1967-1971
      - Trade with Cuba, 1967-1969
      - Trade with satellites, 1962-1971
      - Trade with Soviet Union, 1965-1977, (2 folders)
      - Young Americans for Freedom, information and action material, 1968, (2 folders)
    - The Exchange, periodical
      - circa 1962-1968, (2 folders)
      - 1969-1977 (Box 797)
    - Federal Budget Coalition, 1976
    - Foreign travel, 1976
    - Freedom Review, periodical, 1965-1967
    - Friedman, Milton, circa 1960, 1968-1970
    - "Future United States Foreign Trade Policy," Roth report, 1969
    - Good speeches, 1968-1970
    - Humor, 1969, undated
    - Illinois Central Railroad, 1965-1968, (2 folders)